### EMMANUEL NWANUOGOR

& <u>08037496578</u> @ <u>emmyboi2010@yahoo.com</u>

#### **Profiles**

Customer Experience Analyst/ Frontend Engineer

A goal oriented individual with good collaborative team spirit and effective interpersonal relationship. A problem solving specialists with over 4 years experience in customer service and a dynamic professional. A self sufficiency motivated and solution oriented individual with high ethical standard, good in negotiating, communication skills and a team player with a will to develop capacity for smart work, can multitask

### **Experience**

SunKing

**Customer service Executive** 

Nov2021 -present

Nigeria

- Customer relationship development and management.
- Customer education on the company's products and services. Languages.
- Timely first contact response to customers' enquiries. Resolution of customers' queries and complaints.
- Effective customer account management using CRM and other frontline applications. Collate and report feedback from customers on the performance of the company's products and services.
- Identify customers' needs, carpi information, research every issue and provide solutions and/or alternative Seize opportunities to upsell

Union Bank Plc Jan-2020-Nov2021

Customer service Executive

Nigeria

- Build sustainable relationships and engage customers by taking the extra mile.
- Frequently attend educational training to improve knowledge.
- Meet personal/team qualitative and quantitative targets.
- Manage large amounts of phone calls (inbound and outbound), chats, emails, and other communication channels
- Ensure customer satisfaction and maintain professional customer support

### **Education**

### Federal Polytechnic Nasarawa

**HND** 

Banking and Finance

Jan 2015- Dec 2017

Federal Polytechnic Nasarawa

ND

Nov 2011- Dec2013 Banking and Finance

**Tech Studio Academy** 

wed development

Frontend

2021-2022

**Vephla University** 

2024

Wed Development

Frontend Engineering

### References

# Rvailable upon request.

# Skills

HTML

•••• **CSS** 

JavaScript • • • • •

Data centricity

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$ 

Digital literacy

**Problem-solving** 

. . . . .

Data centricity

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$ 

Collaboration

••••

Ability to gauge client needs

Team player

**Communication Skills** 

. . . . .

MS Excel and MS Word

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$ 

React Js • • 0 0 0

# **Interests**

Travelling and meet new people, Music, Sport

**CIBN** Certifications 2016 student member